Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/tinnguyennct (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

PostgreSQL MongoDB Kong API Gateway

Certifications

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate

Tin Nguyen

DevOps Engineer

Vietnam

Summary

With 5 years of experience in the role of a System/DevOps engineer. I'm responsible for researching, deploying, and operating systems, as well as automating application deployment processes. Have experienced in developing and operating large-scale systems with the knowledge and experience in building product from inception to real products.

Experience

FPT Retail
DevOps Engineer
April 2024 - Present (1 year)

Nha Khoa Kim - Kim Dental DevOps Engineer April 2021 - March 2024 (3 years) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

LCS Group DevOps Engineer June 2022 - June 2023 (1 year 1 month)

LCS Group System Engineer June 2018 - March 2021 (2 years 10 months) System Engineer

IDB VoIP Technician February 2018 - May 2018 (4 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

University of Transport and Communication - HCMC Engineer's degree, Electronics and Communication Engineering · (September 2013 - January 2018)